searchamong.com 2013-05-01

# SearchAmong - Privacy Policy

**Privacy policy**

This privacy policy applies to the SearchAmong Software and each of the related Web sites (the "Web Sites") maintained by SearchAmong  ("we" or "us"). In the event of any inconsistency between this privacy policy and a policy listed on one of the other Web Sites, this policy shall control. 

We do not collect personally identifiable information including names, address', phone numbers. We do not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information you provide when using the SearchAmong  Software or the Web Sites.

We gather certain information such as internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser user agent, referring page, date/time stamp and cookies automatically. We use such information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information to better provide our services. 

When you visit the SearchAmong  Web Sites, we may place a small text file-called a "cookie"-on your computer that allows us to improve the quality of our service, and to store your preferences and settings. Importantly, a cookie does not allow us to obtain any personally identifiable information (such as your real name or address) unless you have specifically provided such information when using the Web Sites or the Software. The search feature sends a request to our servers while processing a search query that you have inputted. This request includes the keyword query from the browser toolbar and all HTTP data transferred automatically by the browser (IP Address, User Agent, Cookies, etc…). We use this information in order to properly process your search request.
